The following content is provided
提供以下内容
under a Creative Commons license.
根据知识共享许可。
Your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue
您的支持将帮助MIT OpenCourseWare继续
to offer high quality educational resources for free.
免费提供高质量的教育资源。
To make a donation, or view additional materials
捐款或查看其他材料
from hundreds of MIT courses, visit MIT OpenCourseWare
从数百门麻省理工学院的课程中，访问MIT OpenCourseWare
at ocw.mit.edu.
在ocw.mit.edu。
PROFESSOR: So you guys know the quiz is cumulative, right?
教授：所以你们知道测验是累积的，对吧？
Everything all the way back from lecture one,
从第一讲开始的一切，
so I would look at all the lectures and all the P sets,
所以我会看所有的讲座和所有的P套，
and look at all the stuff that we taught you,
看看我们教给你的所有东西，
so data structures, algorithms, everything.
数据结构，算法，一切。
And at least be able to know, for every one of them,
至少对每个人都知道
what's the name, what it does, and wants the running time.
名称是什么，它的作用是什么，需要运行时间。
Proofs and how it does it might be harder,
证明及其执行方式可能会更困难，
but these be able to call it as a black box
但这些人可以将其称为黑匣子
and argue about the running times.
并讨论运行时间。
So I have a dp problem, and I have a non-dp problem.
所以我有一个dp问题，而我有一个非dp问题。
Which problem would you like me to start with?
您希望我从哪个问题开始？
OK.
好。
Do you guys know the saying, if a woodchucker would chuck wood,
你们知道吗，如果一个啄木鸟会夹木头，
how much wood would a woodchucker chuck?
啄木鸟会吸多少木头？
Today we're going to chuck wood.
今天我们要去掉木头。
So you have a piece of wood that is l meters long,
所以你有一块木头，长一米
and they have n markings.
他们有n个标记。
So say the first mark is at 3 meters,
假设第一个标记位于3米处，
the second mark is at 5 meters, so on, so forth.
第二个标记位于5米处，依此类推。
And 3, and 4, all the way up to mn.
和3和4，一直到mn。
So we want to cut this piece of wood at all the markings.
因此，我们想在所有标记处切这块木头。
The thing is the woodchucker doesn't work for free.
事情是，土拨鼠不是免费工作的。
If you give it a piece of wood of length l,
如果给它一块长度为l的木头，
and you ask it to cut it at some marking,
然后您要求它在某些标记处进行切割，
you're going to get two pieces of wood, length l1 and l2.
您将得到两块长度分别为l1和l2的木头。
The price for this is l1 times l2.
价格是l1乘以l2。
So we like woodchucker, but woodchuckers would also
所以我们喜欢啄木鸟，但是啄木鸟也会
like our wallets.
像我们的钱包。
So we want to cut this up by paying
所以我们想通过支付来削减
the minimum amount of money.
最低金额。
Rings a bell?
摇铃？
So I'll let you guys think for a minute,
所以我让你们思考一分钟，
then I'll give you the running time, then we'll start talking.
然后我给您运行时间，然后我们开始讨论。
So we usually give you running times on quizzes.
因此，我们通常会根据测验为您提供跑步时间。
The running time is why you should know all the problems
运行时间就是为什么您应该了解所有问题的原因
in their matching running times, because the moment we give you
在他们匹配的运行时间中，因为我们给您的那一刻
a running time you can automatically eliminate all
运行时间可以自动消除所有
the things that don't match, and just focus on a few things.
不匹配的东西，只专注于一些东西。
So you're going to have to cut it at all the markings,
因此，您将不得不在所有标记处将其切开，
eventually, but the order in which you cut is important.
最终，但是剪切顺序很重要。
So if I cut here first, then I'm going to pay three times l
所以，如果我先在这里砍，那我要付三倍
minus 3, whereas if I cut in the middle first,
减3，而如果我先切入中间，
I'm going to pay whatever this is, and 3 times l minus m3.
我要付这是什么，三倍我减去m3。
So we're trying to decide the order.
因此，我们正在尝试确定顺序。
Does this look like any familiar problem?
这看起来像任何熟悉的问题吗？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE] using dp, right?
听众：[听不清]使用dp，对吗？
PROFESSOR: dp, that is good.
教授：dp，很好。
I did say that we're going to start with a dp problem,
我确实说过我们将从dp问题开始，
so this is dp.
所以这是dp。
It's a good start.
这是一个好的开始。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE]
观众：[听不清]
PROFESSOR: What?
教授：什么？
Not exactly.
不完全是。
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
PROFESSOR: So, it is not like any problems
教授：所以这不是任何问题
on the recitations.
在朗诵中。
So far recitations did prefixes and suffixes.
到目前为止，背诵都有前缀和后缀。
We're going to solve this using a running time of n
我们将使用n的运行时间来解决这个问题
cubed, which is like the parenthesis problem.
立方，就像括号问题一样。
It should be what you said, but I don't know how to spell that,
它应该是您所说的，但我不知道该如何拼写，
so we're going to go for this instead.
因此，我们将改为这样做。
So running n cubed-- the moment I
因此，当我运行n立方时
said this you guys should know that this
说这个，你们应该知道
is the n cubed problem that we have in lecture notes.
是我们在讲义中的第n个立方问题。
So make sure to have those on the cheat sheets,
因此，请确保备忘单上有这些内容，
and try to understand them, right?
并尝试了解它们，对吗？
OK, so given that I've said this,
好的，鉴于我已经说过了，
you should know the solution now.
您现在应该知道解决方案。
To make sure everyone is with me,
为了确保每个人都和我在一起，
we're going to go through the solution, whole.
整个过程，我们将通过解决方案。
So what is a subproblem?
那么什么是子问题？
AUDIENCE:Smaller piece of wood.
听众：一块木头很小。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
AUDIENCE: Like how to cut it up.
听众：喜欢怎么剪。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So this is how you think of it informally.
因此，这就是您非正式地考虑的方式。
When you write it up, I want to see this.
当您写下来时，我想看看。
I want to see dp of something means something.
我想看到dp代表某种意义。
So how you fill out your dp table.
那么如何填写dp表。
It's really useful to write this up on your exam
在考试中写下来真的很有用
before, because one, this will help you write the recursion
以前，因为这可以帮助您编写递归
correctly, and two, if the grader sees this
正确，还有两个，如果平地机看到了
they might skim over the recursion completely.
他们可能会完全浏览递归。
And then you might have bugs there.
然后，您可能在那里遇到了错误。
We might not see them.
我们可能看不到它们。
Good for you.
对你有好处。
So this says how you're going to fill out the table.
因此，这说明您将如何填写表格。
Right? dp of something equals something.
对？某物的dp等于某物。
What's in a dp table?
dp表中有什么？
Numbers.
数字。
It's never how to do something.
从来没有做某事。
It's always the numbers, so it's always
总是数字，所以总是
the maximum profit, or the minimum cost,
最大利润或最小成本，
or the shortest distance, or the longest something.
或最短的距离，或最长的东西。
So it's always a number.
所以它总是一个数字。
So what we do here?
那么我们在这里做什么？
AUDIENCE: Start and dp, start location to the end location is
听众：开始和dp，开始位置到结束位置为
PROFESSOR: OK, so we're going to get the mean distance, right?
教授：好的，我们将获得平均距离，对吗？
We usually do i j k and whatever else it takes.
我们通常会进行ijk以及其他任何操作。
So start to end is?
那么开始到底是什么？
AUDIENCE: The minimum cost of cutting that up.
听众：削减成本的最低成本。
PROFESSOR: Minimum cost of cutting up the wood board
教授：切木板的最低成本
from marking i, all the way to marking j.
从标记i一直到标记j。
There's a tiny problem here, that the initial-- there's
这里有一个小问题，最初的-
no problem for this big piece of wood, right?
这块大木头没问题吧？
If I can only consider the board from i to j,
如果我只能考虑从i到j的董事会，
so if I can only consider the board from marking 1
因此，如果我只能考虑标记1
to marking n, then I get to this.
标记n，然后我就知道了
So this part and this part get left out.
所以这部分和这部分被忽略了。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE]
观众：[听不清]
PROFESSOR: Exactly.
教授：是的。
We add fake markings.
我们添加了假标记。
Then 0 is 0, and mn plus 1 equals l.
那么0是0，并且mn加1等于l。
Very good.
很好。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE] equally spaced?
听众：[听不清]等距？
PROFESSOR: No.
教授：不。
So these are numbers.
这些是数字。
If they were evenly spaced, I think there's an algorithm.
如果它们均匀分布，我认为有一种算法。
You might come up with a math and say, you always
您可能想出一个数学说，您总是
cut it up like this.
切成这样
So while we solve this, you guys have candy, right?
所以当我们解决这个问题时，你们有糖果，对吗？
You should eat the candy and be energetic and everything.
您应该吃糖果，并且精力充沛。
So min cost of cutting up the board
所以最小的成本削减董事会
from marking i to marking j.
从标记i到标记j。
I like this.
我喜欢这个。
Have this on your exam if possible,
如有可能，请在考试中进行检查，
because this will make our life easier,
因为这会使我们的生活更轻松，
and it's going to make your life easier
这将使您的生活更轻松
when you get to the next step, which
当您进行下一步时，
is how do we compute dp of i j?
如何计算ij的dp？
So suppose I'm looking at the subboard from m1 to m4
因此，假设我正在查看从m1到m4的子板
so I'm looking at only this.
所以我只看这个。
How do I compute the best way to cut the board from m1 to m4?
如何计算将木板从m1切成m4的最佳方法？
What are my options?
我有什么选择？
AUDIENCE: The locations you can cut it.
听众：您可以剪切的位置。
PROFESSOR: Exactly.
教授：是的。
So in order to cut this up, I can either
所以为了削减这个，我可以
make a first cut at m2.
在m2处进行第一次切割。
So say I make my first cut here, and then I
所以说我先在这里切，然后我
recursively cut this, and cut this.
递归剪切，然后剪切。
Or the other alternative is take the same guy-- m1,
或者另一个选择是请同一个人-m1，
m2, m3, m4-- cut it at m3, and then recursively cut this,
m2，m3，m4--将其剪切为m3，然后递归剪切，
and recursively cut this.
并递归地削减它。
So I'm iterating over all the markings inside the board.
因此，我要遍历板上的所有标记。
Now suppose I'm cutting it-- yes?
现在假设我要剪掉了-是吗？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE] cutting both, or actually, never mind.
听众：[听不清]两者兼而有之，或者没关系。
PROFESSOR: Yeah, when I recursed,
教授：是的，当我递归时，
that takes care of it.
照顾它。
So suppose I'm looking at m1 through m4,
所以假设我正在看m1到m4，
and I'm cutting it at m2.
我要把它削减到m2
What's the total cost?
总费用是多少？
So what's the best way to cut, given that then I
那么，鉴于这种情况，最好的切割方法是什么
know I'm going to cut there?
知道我要去那里切吗？
AUDIENCE: The sum of the dp's.
听众：dp之和。
PROFESSOR: OK, so it's the best way to cut m1 through m2,
教授：好的，所以这是将m1切成m2的最好方法，
plus best way to cut m2 through m4,
加上将m2减少到m4的最佳方法，
plus the price I'm paying for this cut, right?
再加上我要为此减价支付的价格，对吗？
Not just the sum of the dp's.
不只是dp的总和。
One more term.
还有一个学期。
What's this term?
这是什么意思
AUDIENCE: 4 minus 1?
听众：4减1？
Or the location of 4 minus the location of 1.
或4的位置减去1的位置。
PROFESSOR: So, not quite, almost.
教授：所以，不完全是。
So if I'm cutting a board into two pieces,
因此，如果我将一块木板切成两块，
the cost is the product of the length of the two pieces.
成本是两个零件长度的乘积。
m2 minus m1, times yes.
m2减去m1，乘以是。
OK, why did I bother doing this?
好，我为什么要这么做呢？
Some people think better with concrete numbers.
有些人认为具体数字会更好。
If that's the case, then give yourself an example.
如果是这样，请给自己一个例子。
Write some numbers on your sheet of paper,
在纸上写一些数字，
then see what letters match to what
然后看什么字母和什么字母匹配
numbers, and copy it up using letters.
数字，然后使用字母复制。
And there you go, you've solved the problem.
至此，您已经解决了问题。
So where are i and j here?
那么我和j在哪里？
AUDIENCE: i would be 1.
听众：我会是1。
PROFESSOR: OK, so this is i.
教授：好的，这就是我。
AUDIENCE: That's j.
听众：是j。
PROFESSOR: Cool, so let's try to write it up, now.
教授：太好了，现在让我们尝试编写它。
So in order to cut the board from i to j, what am I doing?
因此，为了将董事会从i削减到j，我在做什么？
So what am I computing?
那我在计算什么呢？
Usually the first word in your subproblem definition
通常，子问题定义中的第一个单词
is the function that you're going to use.
是您将要使用的功能。
So it's minimum, and I'm going iterate over something.
因此，这是最低要求，我将迭代某些内容。
AUDIENCE: dp of i to-- it has to be all of j.
听众：我的dp必须是j的全部。
dp of i, j, and you're looking to--
i，j的dp，您正在寻找-
PROFESSOR: So I'm computing dp of i j.
教授：所以我正在计算i j的dp。
AUDIENCE: I know, of j minus [INAUDIBLE].
听众：我知道，j减[听不清]。
AUDIENCE: j minus i, then k j minus [INAUDIBLE].
听众：j减去i，然后kj减去[音频不清晰]。
PROFESSOR: There's a k, right?
教授：有，对吧？
I need a new variable for where I'm going to cut up, right?
我需要在要切入的位置使用新变量，对吗？
So fortunately, we have a lot of letters in the alphabet,
幸运的是，我们的字母表中有很多字母，
i, j, k, so on and so forth, l, m.
i，j，k，依此类推，l，m。
AUDIENCE: i plus k.
听众：我加k。
PROFESSOR: So let's say that k is the place where
教授：那么说k是
we cut, to make our life easy.
我们削减，使我们的生活轻松。
So I'm going to have dp of
所以我要有dp
AUDIENCE: Well i is the starting point.
听众：好吧，我是起点。
PROFESSOR: OK
教授：好的
AUDIENCE: And then, the endpoint is i plus k, right?
听众：然后，端点是i加k，对吗？
PROFESSOR: So what's k here?
教授：那这里是什么？
AUDIENCE: k is an actual number.
听众：k是实际数字。
It's not the offset, it's the actual number,
不是偏移量，而是实际数字，
so it should be i to k.
所以应该是我到k。
It depends how you define k.
这取决于您如何定义k。
PROFESSOR: So I'm going to make my life easy, and define k
教授：所以我要让我的生活轻松一点，并定义k
as exactly the marking at which I cut.
恰好是我切割的标记。
k is this 2 here.
k是这里的2。
And this is easier, trust me.
这更容易，相信我。
OK, plus?
好，再加上？
AUDIENCE: k j?
听众：kj？
PROFESSOR: OK, and?
教授：好吧？
AUDIENCE: Cost of m--
听众：m的费用-
AUDIENCE: j minus i, m of k minus m of i times m of j
听众：j减去i，k的m减去i的m乘以j的m
minus m of k.
减去k。
PROFESSOR: Cool.
教授：太好了。
Yeah, other way around-- doesn't matter.
是的，其他方法都没关系。
So now where does k go?
那么，现在k去哪里？
We have to come up with numbers for the loop, right?
我们必须为循环提供数字，对吗？
AUDIENCE: Between i and j.
听众：在i和j之间。
AUDIENCE: j minus i.
听众：j减去i。
AUDIENCE: Just for k in i to j.
听众：只为从i到j的k个。
PROFESSOR: So if I have the board from 1 to 4,
教授：如果我的董事会人数从1到4，
do I cut at 1?
我削减1？
I can, but that's kind of weird.
我可以，但这有点奇怪。
Because I'm recursing on the same subproblem.
因为我要递归相同的子问题。
By the way, if you recurse to the same subproblem,
顺便说一句，如果递归到相同的子问题，
what are you going to get as your running time?
您的跑步时间将获得什么？
Infinite.
无穷。
So let's not do that.
因此，我们不要这样做。
So we're going to go from?
所以我们要去哪里？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE]
观众：[听不清]
PROFESSOR: So going from i would be bad.
教授：所以从我那里去是不好的。
So i plus 1.
所以我加1。
2?
2？
AUDIENCE: j minus 1.
听众：j减1。
PROFESSOR: Very good.
教授：非常好。
AUDIENCE: Would it be m over i plus 1, because [INAUDIBLE].
听众：是[我听不清]，所以我等于1。
PROFESSOR: So k is which marking I'm cutting at.
教授：那么k是我要剪切的标记。
I never want to cut inside a marking.
我永远都不想在标记内切。
However, I don't even know these are integers.
但是，我什至不知道这些是整数。
AUDIENCE: They wouldn't be called [INAUDIBLE].
听众：他们不会被称为[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: So k is which marking, i, j,
教授：那么k是哪个标记i，j，
and k are which marking I'm cutting at.
和k是我要剪切的标记。
These are the only discrete things I have.
这些是我唯一的离散事物。
This board is all filled with real numbers.
这块木板全都是实数。
So if I want to cut somewhere here,
所以如果我想在这里切某处，
that's a real number-- I don't like that.
那是一个真实的数字-我不喜欢那样。
I want to have integers.
我想要整数。
So my markings help me get integers.
所以我的标记帮助我获得整数。
I only want to cut at the marking,
我只想切割标记
so I always look at my problem in terms of which marking I'm
所以我总是看我的问题
cutting it.
削减它。
So this always iterates over markings.
因此，这总是遍历标记。
So this looks very much like the parentheses problem, right?
所以这看起来很像括号问题，对吗？
Same subproblems, roughly the same recursion.
相同的子问题，大致相同的递归。
Turns out that these problems, where
原来这些问题，在哪里
you're not considering suffixes or prefixes,
您不考虑后缀或前缀，
but rather you're considering substrings,
而是您正在考虑子字符串，
are reasonably hard to come by, and reasonably hard to solve.
相当困难，也很难解决。
So if we give these to you, chances
因此，如果我们将这些赠予您，
are they're going to be exactly like the parentheses problem,
它们会完全像括号问题一样吗，
except for the cost function.
除了成本函数。
This isn't what we had in the parentheses problem, right?
这不是括号问题中的内容，对吗？
So you should be prepared to solve problems
所以你应该准备解决问题
that look exactly like the paren problem,
看起来完全像是paren问题
but might have a different cost function.
但可能具有不同的成本函数。
And this is how we solve it.
这就是我们解决问题的方式。
OK.
好。
AUDIENCE: When you say that the complexity determines
听众：当您说复杂性决定
which type of dp example we use, does
我们使用哪种类型的dp示例
that mean that a problem can be solved
那意味着一个问题可以解决
using any of dp examples?
使用任何dp示例？
It's just that the only thing that changes is the complexity.
只是唯一改变的是复杂性。
PROFESSOR: I don't think you can map
教授：我认为您无法绘制地图
every approach onto every problem.
解决每个问题的每种方法。
For example, if you tried to map prefixes onto this,
例如，如果您尝试将前缀映射到此地址，
you'd come up with a solution that
你会想出一个解决方案
doesn't look at all the possible choices,
并没有考虑所有可能的选择，
so your answer would be sub-optimal.
因此您的答案将不是最理想的。
So you'd come up with a fast, but incorrect algorithm.
因此，您会想到一种快速但不正确的算法。
However, if you take the problem of find the longest
但是，如果您遇到寻找时间最长的问题
increasing sub-sequence, you can definitely
增加子序列，您绝对可以
apply this technique to it.
运用这项技术。
It's more general than suffixes or prefixes.
它比后缀或前缀更通用。
So it's going to work, but it's going to be slower.
因此它可以工作，但速度会变慢。
So in theory, what you should do is,
因此，从理论上讲，您应该做的是，
you have all these techniques.
您拥有所有这些技巧。
Given a problem, you try all the techniques.
遇到问题，您可以尝试所有技术。
You see which ones apply, and out of those, you
您会看到哪些适用，而其中哪些适用
see which one gives you the best running time.
看看哪一个给您最佳的运行时间。
In practice, if we give you the running time,
实际上，如果我们给您运行时间，
you match it to the techniques that match the running time.
您可以将其与运行时间相匹配的技术进行匹配。
You start backwards from the stuff that you know.
您从已知的内容开始倒退。
OK.
好。
Does this problem make sense?
这个问题有意义吗？
Sweet.
甜。
Now let's do a hard problem.
现在让我们做一个难题。
Do people remember hashing?
人们还记得哈希吗？
You have one minute to remember hashing
你有一分钟​​要记住哈希
while I erase the board.
当我擦除木板时。
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
So suppose we want to implement the set.
因此，假设我们要实现该集合。
The way we're going to implement the set is, we have n elements.
我们要实现集合的方式是，我们有n个元素。
We're going to put them into the set,
我们要把它们放进去，
so for i goes from 1 through n, we're
所以我从1到n
going to insert element i, so first we're
要插入元素i，所以首先
going to insert all the elements into the set.
将所有元素插入集合。
And then after that, given a random number, we want to see
然后，给定一个随机数，我们想看看
is it in the set, or not.
是否在集合中。
So for some other number-- I used n before, so let's
因此，对于其他一些数字，我以前使用过n，所以让我们
use-- for some other number f, we want to see is f in the set,
使用-对于其他一些数字f，我们希望看到集合中的f，
or is f not in the set?
还是f不在集合中？
What data structure would you use normally for this?
您通常会使用什么数据结构？
A hash table, right?
哈希表，对不对？
You stick everything into a hash table,
您将所有内容粘贴到哈希表中，
then you try to find the elements.
然后您尝试查找元素。
If you find them, then you say yes.
如果找到它们，那么您说是。
If not, then you say no.
如果不是，那么您说不。
Well, it turns out that this would
好吧，事实证明这会
take more memory than what we have.
占用比我们更多的内存。
So instead, we're going to do this.
因此，我们将执行此操作。
We're going to have a hash table of m bits.
我们将有一个m位的哈希表。
So these are m bits.
所以这些是m位。
And say we have a hash function that
并说我们有一个哈希函数
satisfies with uniform hashing, so given any element,
满足统一哈希，因此给定任何元素，
the value is anywhere from 0 to m minus 1,
取值范围是0到m减去1，
and they're all independent.
他们都是独立的。
So the way we're going to insert an element
所以我们要插入一个元素的方式
is-- this table is T-- we're going to say that T of h of ai
是-这张表是T-我们要说的是a的h的T
equals 1.
等于1。
So this is a table of bits.
这是位表。
For every element we hash the element,
对于每个元素，我们对元素进行哈希处理，
and we set the corresponding bit to 1.
然后将相应的位设置为1。
So we're going to have some 1s, and some zeros in the table.
因此，我们在表中将有一些1和一些0。
Say if this is ai, it hashes somewhere here.
假设这是ai，它会散列在这里。
OK so the question is, we inserted
好，问题是，我们插入了
n elements into a table of size n.
将n个元素放入大小为n的表中。
Given a new element, f, where f stands for false positive-- f
给定一个新元素f，其中f代表假阳性-f
is not one of the elements that we inserted.
不是我们插入的元素之一。
I want to know what's the probability that the set will
我想知道布景的可能性是多少
say that the element is in the set, so basically,
说元素在集合中，所以基本上
the probability of a false positive.
误报的概率。
AUDIENCE: So what are we doing about [INAUDIBLE]?
听众：那么我们对[听不清]怎么办？
PROFESSOR: Nothing.
教授：没事。
AUDIENCE: Is it chaining, is it open addressing?
听众：是链接，是开放地址吗？
Does it even matter?
有关系吗
PROFESSOR: So we're not inserting the elements
教授：所以我们不会插入元素
into the table.
进入桌子。
This table only has bits.
该表只有位。
The elements are lost completely after we insert them.
插入元素后，这些元素将完全丢失。
So the tradeoff is uses a lot less memory.
因此，折衷方案是使用更少的内存。
Instead of having to store entire elements,
不必存储整个元素，
you just store bits.
你只是存储位。
On the downside you're going to have false positives.
不利的一面是您会误报。
Because if I have a different element,
因为如果我有不同的元素，
say f, if it hashes to the same location,
说f，如果它哈希到相同的位置，
then the set is going to say, yeah, it's in the set.
然后场景会说，是的，它在场景中。
So you get false positives.
因此，您会得到误报。
Would you get false negatives?
您会得到假阴性吗？
No, right?
没有权利？
Because you start out with a table of 0's,
因为您以0的表格开始，
and you only set the table to ones
而且您只将表格设置为
for the numbers that match to hashes
匹配哈希的数字
of elements that are in the set.
集合中的元素。
Did you have a question?
你有问题吗
OK.
好。
OK, do we understand the problem,
好，我们了解问题了吗
before we attempt to solve it?
在我们尝试解决它之前？
AUDIENCE: Is it probably 1/m?
听众：大概是1 / m吗？
PROFESSOR: You'd wish, but no.
教授：您希望，但不能。
AUDIENCE: It's less than n/m.
听众：小于n / m。
PROFESSOR: OK, I like that.
教授：好的，我喜欢。
So what are you thinking?
那你在想什么
AUDIENCE: If there are no collisions previously,
观众：如果以前没有碰撞，
then it would equal to n/m, but there are collisions, probably
那么它等于n / m，但是可能有碰撞
collisions.
碰撞。
PROFESSOR: OK, I'm going to open up a window in your head
教授：好的，我要在你脑海中打开一个窗口
and tell everyone else the small steps you took to get here.
并告诉其他人您到达这里所采取的小步骤。
So we have this new number f.
因此，我们有了这个新数字f。
How are we going to check if it's in the set or not?
我们如何检查它是否在集合中？
We're going to compute h of f, and we're
我们将计算f的h，
going to check if t of h of f is 0 or 1.
将检查f的h中的t是否为0或1。
f is different from all the other elements.
f与所有其他元素不同。
So its hash value is independent from all the other hash values
因此，其哈希值与所有其他哈希值无关
we had before.
我们以前有过。
We don't really care about this anymore,
我们真的不再关心这个了
after we have the independence assumption.
在我们有独立性假设之后。
So h of f is just some random position in the table.
因此，f的h只是表中的一些随机位置。
So the question is, given some random position in the table,
所以问题是，给定表中的一些随机位置，
will that be a 0 or a 1?
那是0还是1？
How do you know?
你怎么知道的？
If I knew how many 1's I have in the table--
如果我知道桌上有多少个1-
if I have k 1's in the table, and automatically this means n
如果我在表中有k 1，这自动意味着n
minus k 0's-- then what's the probability that h of f will
减去k 0-那么f的h的概率是多少
point to a 1?
指向1？
AUDIENCE: k/m.
观众：k / m。
PROFESSOR: Yes.
教授：是的。
So the hash takes m possible values.
因此，散列取m个可能的值。
k of them are 1's.
其中k为1。
So the probability that the hash is going to guess a 1 is k/m.
因此，哈希猜测为1的概率为k / m。
So if we knew how many 1's we have, then this is the answer.
因此，如果我们知道我们有多少个1，那么这就是答案。
We know that we're going to have at most n 1's-- that's what
我们知道我们最多将有n 1个-这就是
you're thinking, right?
你在想吧？
So k is definitely smaller or equal to n,
因此，k绝对小于或等于n，
so the answer definitely has to be smaller or equal than n/m.
因此答案肯定必须小于或等于n / m。
Now if you're in a rush, you might say,
现在，如果您很着急，您可能会说，
well, we inserted n elements, so we're definitely
好吧，我们插入了n个元素，所以我们肯定
going to have n 1's here.
这里要有n 1个
That is not true.
那是不对的。
The hashes of all the elements are independent.
所有元素的哈希都是独立的。
So there is some probability that two elements will
因此，有两个元素可能会
hash to the same value, and as the number of elements grows,
散列为相同的值，并且随着元素数量的增加，
that probability also grows.
这种可能性也会增加。
OK, so now by looking at this, we
好的，所以现在看这个，我们
got rid of this part of the problem.
摆脱了这部分问题。
We don't care that there's a new element.
我们不在乎有一个新元素。
We don't care that it's a false positive.
我们不在乎这是一个误报。
All that we care about is how many
我们只关心多少
1's do we have in the table after inserting n values.
插入n个值后，我们在表中得到1。
Well, what's that?
恩那是什么
That's m times the probability that a slot in the table is 1.
这是表中插槽为1的概率的m倍。
Right, the probability that the slot in the table is 1 is k/m.
正确，表格中的广告位为1的概率为k / m。
So if we know this probability, and we multiply it by m,
因此，如果我们知道这个概率，并将其乘以m，
then we get k.
那么我们得到k。
People still with me?
人们还和我在一起吗？
AUDIENCE: And what does that variable represent, h?
听众：那个变量代表什么？
PROFESSOR: This is k.
教授：这是k。
Represents that my handwriting sucks, basically.
基本上代表我的笔迹很烂。
AUDIENCE: I mean, why do we do m times the probability.
听众：我的意思是，为什么我们做概率是m倍。
That's the the expected number of 1's in the table?
那是表中预期的数字1？
PROFESSOR: Yeah.
教授：是的。
Yeah, this is E of k, I guess.
是的，我猜这是k的E。
So then our final answer is this thing divided by m.
因此，我们的最终答案是这东西除以m。
So the answer is the expected value of k,
所以答案是k的期望值
or you can just think of it as the average value of k, divided
或者您可以将其视为k的平均值除以
by m.
按米
So this is m times this probability, divided by m.
因此，这是该概率的m倍除以m。
So it is exactly this probability.
因此，正是这种可能性。
So the thing that we want to focus on
所以我们要重点关注的是
is, what's the probability that a random slot in the table
是，表格中的随机广告位的概率是多少
is a 1?
是1？
AUDIENCE: It's equal to 1 minus the probability
听众：等于1减去概率
that it was never fixed.
从来没有解决过。
PROFESSOR: Exactly, the first thing we do.
教授：确实，我们要做的第一件事。
1 minus the probability that a slot is 0.
1减去广告位为0的概率。
This is easy, right, like it looks easy.
这很容易，对，就像看起来很容易。
But this makes a huge difference,
但这有很大的不同，
because once we're here, well, a slot is zero
因为一旦我们来到这里，广告位为零
if none of the insertions made it a one.
如果没有一个插入使其成为一个。
And the insertions are all independent.
并且插入都是独立的。
So this is like, you're flipping a coin.
就像您要掷硬币一样。
What's the probability that after you flip it n times,
翻转n次后，出现几率的几率是多少
you never get a head?
你永远不会头脑好吗？
So this is 1 minus
所以这是1减
AUDIENCE: 1 over m to the something.
听众：1以上的东西。
PROFESSOR: That-- So a slot is 0 means
教授：那-插槽为0表示
that no number was inserted in it.
没有插入任何数字。
We're inserting n numbers, so it's the probability
我们要插入n个数字，这就是概率
that a single number was not necessarily
单数不一定
in the slot, raised to the power of n.
在插槽中，升至n的幂。
So we have n independent experiments, right?
所以我们有n个独立实验，对不对？
Every time you insert a number into the hash function,
每次将数字插入哈希函数时，
that's one experiment.
那是一个实验。
The hash function gives you independent values
哈希函数为您提供独立的值
for all the elements.
对于所有元素。
So all the insertions are independent of each other.
因此，所有插入都彼此独立。
If, in a single insertion, you've hit that slot,
如果您一次插入该插槽，
then you've made it a 1-- game over.
那么您已经将其打成1局了。
So the slot is only a zero if none of the insertions
因此，如果没有插入，则插槽仅是零
make it the 1.
使其成为1。
So you take the probability that the insertion doesn't
因此，您有可能不会插入
make it a one, and you raise it to the power n,
将其设为1，然后将其提升为n，
because that has to happen n times in order
因为那必须发生n次
for the whole thing to be successful.
才能使整个事情成功。
And the probability that the number was not
那个数字不是
inserted in a slot is 1 minus the probability
插入插槽中是1减去概率
that it was inserted.
它被插入。
Right, we're doing this again.
是的，我们再做一次。
1 minus probability that a number hit.
1减数字命中的概率。
Well what this probability?
那么这个概率是多少？
Uniform hashing.
统一哈希。
AUDIENCE: 1/m
观众：1 / m
PROFESSOR: 1/m.
教授：1 / m。
So this whole thing is 1 minus 1 minus 1, over m to the power n.
因此，整件事是1减去1减去1，超过m等于幂n。
1 minus m minus 1, over m to the power n.
1减去m减去1，将m乘以n。
AUDIENCE: Can we go through this again.
听众：我们可以再经历一次。
From 1 minus probability of a slot is 0, to 1
从1减去槽的概率为0到1
minus probability of a number was not inserted in a slot?
插槽中未插入数字的可能性是否为负？
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So first off, the point of the problem.
所以首先，问题的重点。
It's our problem, right?
是我们的问题吧？
Don't panic, don't be angry.
不要惊慌，不要生气。
You're not going to have some this hard on the exam.
您不会在考试中遇到一些困难。
The point of this is, I want to go through probabilities
重点是，我想通过概率
a little bit, and I want to go through hashing
一点，我想进行散列
and the math behind hashing.
以及哈希背后的数学原理。
Because remembering that will be useful.
因为记住那会很有用。
OK, so now you said you're having trouble with this step?
好的，所以现在您说您在执行此步骤时遇到了麻烦？
OK, so let's see.
好，让我们看看。
Let's do this here.
让我们在这里做。
So we have this table here, right?
所以我们在这里有这张桌子，对吧？
And we have n elements-- e1, e2, e3, all the way through en.
我们有n个元素-e1，e2，e3，一直到en。
How do we put them in the table?
我们如何将它们放在桌子上？
We hash each of them, and each of them maps
我们哈希每个，每个映射
to a random slot in the table.
到表格中的随机位置。
If these are the slots, then e1 might map here,
如果这些是插槽，则e1可能会映射到此处，
e2 might map here, e3 might map here,
e2可能会映射到这里，e3可能会映射到这里，
e4 might map here, so on and so forth.
e4可能会在此处映射，依此类推。
So I have arrows, right?
所以我有箭吧？
Every time I do a hash, that's going to set something to a 1.
每次我进行哈希运算时，都会将值设置为1。
The numbers don't necessarily map to different slots,
数字不一定映射到不同的插槽，
because each number, on its own, maps to a random slot.
因为每个数字都单独映射到一个随机广告位。
So these are all going to be ones.
所以这些都是。
And everything else becomes zero.
其他所有东西都变为零。
If no number maps to a slot, it is 0.
如果没有数字映射到插槽，则为0。
OK, let's look at one slot, any slot.
好，让我们看一个插槽，任何插槽。
So let's say I'm looking at this slot over here.
假设我在这里看这个广告位。
Can you guys see, by the way?
你们可以看到吗？
OK, so let's look at this guy here.
好，让我们在这里看看这个家伙。
What's the probability that it's a 0?
它为0的几率是多少？
So the probability that the slot is
因此，该广告位是
a 0 is the probability that the first number didn't
0是第一个数字没有出现的概率
map to it-- otherwise it would be a 1-- e1
映射到它-否则它将是1-e1
didn't hash to that slot.
没有哈希到该插槽。
e2 also couldn't match to that slot, right?
e2也无法与该插槽匹配，对吗？
So it's the probability that e1 didn't hash to the slot,
这就是e1没有散列到插槽的可能性，
and e2 didn't hash into slot, and e3
和e2没有散列到插槽中，而e3
didn't hash into the slot, so on so forth, right?
没有散​​列到插槽中，依此类推，对吧？
All the way up until en didn't hash to the slot.
一直到en没有散列到该插槽为止。
This makes sense?
这有道理吗？
Now these are all independent events,
现在这些都是独立的事件，
because all the hashes are independent,
因为所有哈希都是独立的，
by the uniform hashing assumption.
通过统一的哈希假设。
So then I can turn ands into products.
这样我便可以将ands变成产品。
So I can say that this equals to the probability
所以我可以说这等于概率
that e1 didn't hash into the slot, times the probability
e1没有散列到插槽中，乘以概率
that e2 didn't hash into the slot, times the probability
e2没有散列到插槽中，乘以概率
that e3 didn't hash into the slot, so on and so forth,
e3没有散列到插槽中，依此类推，
all the way to the probability that en didn't hash.
一直到en没有散列的可能性。
So since I'm dealing with the same hash function,
因此，由于我要处理相同的哈希函数，
turns out that all the probabilities are the same.
事实证明，所有概率都是相同的。
So there, the probability that some fixed number
因此，有一些固定数字的概率
didn't hash, to the power n.
没有散​​列到力量n。
So this is how I got from here to here.
这就是我从这里到这里的方式。
Probabilities and the properties of hashes and hashing
散列和散列的概率以及性质
assumptions.
假设。
So you guys should have those on your cheat sheet,
所以你们应该在备忘单上放那些东西，
and maybe if you have time, review probabilities a bit.
也许如果您有时间，请回顾一下概率。
AUDIENCE: What is the probability
听众：几率是多少
that any given one doesn't hash, 1/m?
给定的任何一个都不会散列，1 / m？
So if e1 doesn't hash in that spot,
因此，如果e1不在该位置进行散列，
isn't that probability 1/m?
这个概率不是1 / m吗？
PROFESSOR: Not quite.
教授：不完全是。
You're close, but not quite.
您很亲密，但不完全是。
So you're saying that the probability that e1
所以你说e1的概率
doesn't hash to this slot is 1/m?
不会哈希到这个插槽是1 / m？
AUDIENCE: I guess it's 1 minus 1/m.
听众：我猜是1减去1 / m。
PROFESSOR: Exactly.
教授：是的。
The probability that it would hash here
它会在此处散列的概率
is 1/m, because it has to pick that one slot out
是1 / m，因为它必须选择一个插槽
of n possible slots.
N个可能的广告位。
But if you're just saying, all I want
但是，如果您只是说，我想要的
is that it doesn't hash here, well, it
是它不会在这里散列，嗯，它
means it can hash anywhere else.
表示它可以在其他任何地方散列。
So it has m minus 1 options.
因此它有m减去1个选项。
It can go to any of those m minus 1 places,
它可以去那些m减去1的地方，
just not to that one place.
只是不去那个地方。
So m minus 1 over m.
所以m减去m减去1。
AUDIENCE: It's interesting it went the other direction.
听众：有趣的是它朝另一个方向发展。
Instead of saying, it's 1, it's 1 minus it.
不用说，它是1，是1减去它。
Wouldn't it have been just as easy to go
难道就这么容易
the other direction, or no?
另一个方向，还是没有？
PROFESSOR: No.
教授：不。
Not doing this makes the problem hard,
不这样做会使问题变得棘手，
so that's why we're doing it.
这就是我们这样做的原因。
This kind of flipping is easy to do conceptually,
从概念上讲，这种翻转很容易做到，
but it might make a hard problem into a really easy problem,
但这可能会使难题变得非常简单，
or at least into a do-able problem.
或至少成为一个可行的问题。
AUDIENCE: Isn't it this the same thing?
听众：这不是一回事吗？
I guess maybe not totally.
我想可能不是全部。
PROFESSOR: So it is exactly the same in terms of the math,
教授：在数学上完全一样，
but computing this without turning it into this
但是计算而不把它变成这个
is really hard.
真的很难
AUDIENCE: Any given slot is 1, isn't it
听众：给定的广告位是1，不是吗
kind of like what we just said, except if the probability
有点像我们刚才说的，除非
of any one mapping is 1/m, mapping to a 1, right?
哪一个映射是1 / m，映射到1，对不对？
And then you take 1 over m raised
然后你把米数加1
to the n, that's the probability of it being a 1
到n，这就是它为1的可能性
at that one place, right?
在那个地方吧？
PROFESSOR: No, not quite.
教授：不，不是。
Yeah.
是的
OK, so are we getting this?
好吧，我们明白了吗？
Somewhat?
有些？
Yes?
是？
AUDIENCE: So the probability of a false positive,
听众：因此，假阳性的可能性，
you're saying that's what's the probability that you
你是说那是你的几率
get the 1, if you actually should [INAUDIBLE] the 0.
如果您实际上应该[听不清] 0，则得到1。
It's because multiple things mapped to that one slot, right?
这是因为有多个事物映射到该插槽，对吗？
PROFESSOR: So the probability of a false positive
教授：所以误报的可能性
is the probability that, given a new element, when we hash it
是给定一个新元素时我们对其进行哈希处理的概率
we get the 1.
我们得到1。
The hash of that new element is independent of all
该新元素的哈希值独立于所有
the other hashes.
其他哈希。
AUDIENCE: Then why is it simple in probability
听众：那么为什么概率如此简单
that you get the 1?
你得到1？
PROFESSOR: So if I have a new element,
教授：所以，如果我有一个新要素，
I'm going to compute its hash, and I'm
我要计算它的哈希值，
going to look in the table.
去看表。
If I see a 1, I'm going to say, oh.
如果我看到1，我会说，哦。
AUDIENCE: Oh, it's a new element.
听众：哦，这是一个新元素。
OK.
好。
PROFESSOR: Yeah, so it's something
教授：是的，这就是
that was not in the set.
那不在集合中。
AUDIENCE: OK.
听众：好的。
PROFESSOR: Okay, cool.
教授：好的，很酷。
OK, so let's see if we can do a harder version of this.
好的，让我们看看是否可以对此做一个更硬的版本。
So this probability isn't great, but if we do one trick,
因此，这种可能性并不大，但如果我们采取了一种技巧，
we can make this really nice.
我们可以使它变得非常好。
And this puts together a trick called bloom filters that
这汇集了一个称为Bloom过滤器的技巧
is used in all sorts of situations.
用于各种情况。
So for Bloom filters, we still have n elements,
因此，对于Bloom过滤器，我们仍然有n个元素，
and we still have a table of m bits.
我们还有一张m位的表格
What changes this time is instead of having one function,
这次改变的是没有一个功能，
we have k hash functions.
我们有k个哈希函数。
So when we take an element and insert it,
因此，当我们采用一个元素并将其插入时，
we're taking element i.
我们正在考虑元素i。
The way to insert it is we're going
插入它的方法是我们要
to compute its hash value using all the hash functions,
使用所有哈希函数计算其哈希值，
and set all the corresponding bits to 1.
并将所有相应的位设置为1。
So insert ei becomes, for j in 1 through k,
因此，对于在1至k中的j，插入ei变为
the table bit corresponding to the hash function, j,
对应于哈希函数j的表位，
of the element is 1.
的元素是1。
So each element sets k bits to 1.
因此，每个元素将k位设置为1。
Now how do we check if an element is in the table?
现在我们如何检查表中是否有元素？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE]
观众：[听不清]
PROFESSOR: Since, for every element,
教授：因为，对于每个要素，
we set all the corresponding k bits to 1, now when
我们将所有对应的k位设置为1，现在
we have a new element, we're going
我们有一个新元素，我们要
to compute to the k positions, and if any of them is a 0,
计算到k个位置，如果其中任何一个为0，
then we couldn't have possibly put that in the table.
那么我们不可能将其放在桌子上。
So all T of h j of f have to be 1.
因此f的hj的所有T必须为1。
So for every element, we hashed it k times,
因此，对于每个元素，我们将其散列k次，
and set the corresponding bits.
并设置相应的位。
If we have a new element, and by hashing we get here and here,
如果我们有一个新元素，通过散列，我们可以到达此处和此处，
but we also get here, and this guy was a zero,
但是我们也到了这里，这个家伙是零，
we know we definitely didn't put this in.
我们知道我们绝对没有把它放进去。
So now what's the probability of a false positive?
那么，现在出现误报的概率是多少？
AUDIENCE: My first intuition is just raising that to a power.
听众：我的第一个直觉是将其提升为力量。
AUDIENCE: The probability that when you check--
听众：当您检查-
PROFESSOR: Oh, I forgot to say something, by the way.
教授：哦，我忘了说些什么。
The k hash functions-- I think they satisfy simple uniform
k哈希函数-我认为它们满足简单的统一要求
hashing.
哈希。
I'm not sure if that's the right thing,
我不确定这是否正确，
but they all have independent values from each other.
但是它们彼此之间具有独立的价值。
So they're all independent.
所以他们都是独立的。
So for any number you give, any hash function
因此，对于您给出的任何数字，任何哈希函数
returns a value that's independent of all
返回一个独立于所有值的值
the other hash functions, and they're all 0
其他哈希函数，它们全为0
through n minus 1.
到n减1。
AUDIENCE: Why is not that just raised to something?
听众：为什么不只是提出一些建议？
Because we know the probability-- OK,
因为我们知道可能性-好吧，
actually we need to recalculate that.
实际上我们需要重新计算。
AUDIENCE: Because it's the probability that all of them
听众：因为这是所有人
are 1, even though you haven't hashed yet.
为1，即使您尚未进行哈希处理。
PROFESSOR: So the false positive, the probability
教授：所以误报，概率
of false positives is the probability
误报是概率
that all the k slots that correspond to f are 1's, right?
对应于f的所有k个时隙都是1。
So, since the hash functions are all independent,
因此，由于哈希函数都是独立的，
this is the probability that one slot
这是一个插槽的概率
is the 1, raised to the power k.
是1，提高到幂k。
Right, because they're all independent slots.
是的，因为它们都是独立的插槽。
So it's the probability that one slot
所以这是一个插槽的概率
is a 1, raised to the power k.
是1，提高到幂k。
OK, so now what's the probability
好，那现在有几率
that one slot is a 1?
一个插槽是1？
It looks a lot like this problem, right?
看起来很像这个问题，对吗？
Except there's a tweak.
除非有调整。
How many times did we put the 1 in the table?
我们将1放在表中多少次了？
So here, we put a 1 in the table for every element.
因此，在这里，我们为每个元素在表中放置1。
So we have n sets, right?
所以我们有n套，对吗？
So n times we're going to set t of something to 1.
所以n次我们将把t设置为1。
Right?
对？
For every element, we have one set.
对于每个元素，我们都有一套。
We set one bit to 1.
我们将一位设置为1。
It might have been said before-- that's something else.
之前可能有人说过-那是另外一回事。
Yes?
是？
AUDIENCE: So here it's raised to the m k?
听众：那么，这里已经提高到mk了吗？
PROFESSOR: Yeah, pretty much.
教授：是的，差不多。
So here, for every element we hash it through all the k
所以在这里，对于每个元素，我们将其遍历所有k
functions, and set the corresponding bits to 1.
功能，并将相应的位设置为1。
So one element generates k set operations,
因此，一个元素生成k个set运算，
and we have n elements, so we set n k bits to 1.
并且我们有n个元素，因此我们将nk位设置为1。
Does this make sense?
这有意义吗？
AUDIENCE: Can two hash functions point to the same slot?
听众：两个哈希函数可以指向同一插槽吗？
PROFESSOR: Sure.
教授：当然可以。
But they're all independent, and that's
但是他们都是独立的，那是
the only thing that matters.
唯一重要的事情。
So every time we set the bit, which bit was set
因此，每次设置位时，哪个位被设置
is independent of all the other bits we set,
与我们设置的所有其他位无关，
because all the hash functions are independent,
因为所有哈希函数都是独立的，
and all the values are independent of each other.
并且所有值彼此独立。
So this time, the table size is still m, so that didn't change.
因此，这次表的大小仍然是m，因此没有变化。
This time we set n bits to 1, this time we set n k bits to 1.
这次我们将n位设置为1，这次我们将nk位设置为1。
So then the right thing to do is copy this answer,
因此，正确的做法是复制此答案，
and replace n with n k.
并将n替换为n k。
And if you have to write the proof,
如果您必须写证明，
you'd copy-paste the proof and replace n with n k.
您将复制粘贴证明并将n替换为n k。
So this is 1 minus m minus 1, over m, times n k.
因此，这是1减去m减去1，乘以m乘以n k。
And of course you should go through the whole thing
当然，您应该仔细研究整个过程
in your head and convince yourselves that this is true.
在你的脑海中说服自己，这是真的。
AUDIENCE: Does that say one of the elements is what?
听众：这是否说明要素之一是什么？
k, something?
k，什么？
AUDIENCE: Sets.
观众：集合。
PROFESSOR: Bit sets.
教授：位设置。
So one element sets k bits in the table, not necessarily
因此，一个元素在表中设置了k位，不一定
different bits, just independent bits.
不同的位，只是独立的位。
So if you have n elements altogether,
因此，如果您总共有n个元素，
they set n times k bits.
他们设置n乘以k位。
This thing gets run n times k times, whereas here,
这个东西运行了n次k次，而在这里，
the set operation gets run n times in total.
设置操作总共要运行n次。
That's the difference in the two problems.
那是两个问题的区别。
Right here you have one function for each element,
在这里，每个元素都有一个功能，
here you have k hash functions.
在这里，您有k个哈希函数。
This is hard, right?
这很难，对吗？
Well, it's the hardest hashing problem
好吧，这是最困难的哈希问题
that I could think about and that
我能想到的
makes us go through probabilities and through all
使我们经历概率和所有
the hash stuff.
哈希的东西。
The problems on the exam will be easier, so one, don't panic.
考试中的问题会更容易，所以不要惊慌。
Two, review hashing, review probabilities.
二，查看哈希，查看概率。
When I said, from the theory, this is what you get,
当我说从理论上讲，这就是你所得到的，
if you didn't understand that then please review the theory.
如果您不了解，请复习一下理论。
AUDIENCE: Why is it raised to the k?
听众：为什么将它提高到k？
Because we did down there, if we replace n with n k,
因为我们在那边做了，如果我们用nk代替n，
then we'd just get everything except.
然后我们将得到所有东西，除了。
PROFESSOR: So this thing in here is the answer
教授：所以这是答案
to the previous problem, except you take an n
到前面的问题，除了你拿n
and you replace it with an n k.
然后将其替换为n k
So this is the probability that one bit is set to 1.
因此，这就是将一位设置为1的可能性。
But here, when you're given an element,
但是在这里，当您得到一个元素时，
you're going to hash it through the k functions-- you take
您将通过k函数对其进行哈希处理-
this guy-- you're going to hash it through the k functions,
这个家伙-您将通过k函数对其进行哈希处理，
and you're going to check all the bits.
然后您将检查所有位。
So you're going to check k bits.
因此，您将要检查k位。
So as long as any of the k bits is a zero, not
因此，只要k个位中的任何一个为零，
a false positive.
误报。
So we need all the k bits to be a 1.
所以我们需要所有的k位都为1。
AUDIENCE: Oh, I see.
听众：哦，我知道了。
AUDIENCE: What if the hash functions are dependent?
听众：如果哈希函数是依赖的，该怎么办？
PROFESSOR: Then become intractable.
教授：然后变得棘手。
AUDIENCE: And what if they are?
听众：如果他们呢？
I think the in this problem, the way they are being hashed,
我认为在这个问题上，他们被散列的方式，
that becomes dependent, because I
变得依赖，因为我
think there were some problems where, if something is being
认为有些问题在哪里，如果正在发生
hashed somewhere, then the probability--
散列在某个地方，那么概率-
there could be hash functions that
可能有哈希函数
would put the other thing in the next slot.
会将其他东西放在下一个广告位中。
PROFESSOR: Yes, so you want to reduce these problems
教授：是的，所以您想减少这些问题
to independent hashing.
到独立的哈希。
If you look at the proofs, all the proofs
如果看样张，所有的样张
assume uniform hashing, simple uniform,
假设统一哈希，简单统一，
whatever it takes to get the math down to independence.
无论如何使数学降至独立。
Because this is the only thing that we
因为这是我们唯一的事情
know how to solve with probabilities.
知道如何用概率解决。
If everything is independent, then things
如果一切都是独立的，那么事情
multiply and add up in the right places, and everything is easy.
在正确的地方相乘并相加，一切都很容易。
If things are dependent, then proofs
如果事情是依赖的，那么证明
become really, really hard.
变得非常非常困难。
So whenever you have dependent things,
因此，只要您有依赖的东西，
you want to find a way to reduce that to independent things.
您想找到一种将其简化为独立事物的方法。
Is everyone tired, or do you guys really
大家都累了吗，还是你们真的
not like this problem?
不喜欢这个问题吗？
By the way, really cool trick-- so this
顺便说一句，很酷的技巧-所以这
turns out to be a lot better than that,
事实证明比这要好得多，
and I think the optimal value of k
我认为k的最优值
is around square roots of log n.
在log n的平方根附近。
And that gives you some filters with a really low
这为您提供了一些过滤器
false positive rate.
误报率。
AUDIENCE: What do you mean by optimal?
听众：您所说的最优意味着什么？
PROFESSOR: Minimize the false positives.
教授：尽量减少误报。
So given n and m, pick a case so that this thing is minimized.
因此，给定n和m，请选择一个案例，以使该问题最小化。
AUDIENCE: What was the answer again?
听众：答案又是什么？
Or actually, regardless of that, what's
或实际上，不管怎样，这是什么
the percentage of false positives?
误报的百分比？
PROFESSOR: It depends on what your n and m are, right?
教授：这取决于您的n和m，对吗？
The more bits you can afford
您可以承受的位数更多
AUDIENCE: But if maximize your k,
听众：但是如果最大化k，
you said you came up with some k that's maximized
你说你想出了最大的k
PROFESSOR: I think k is
教授：我认为k是
AUDIENCE: Square root of log n.
听众：日志n的平方根。
AUDIENCE: So then if you use that.
听众：那么如果您使用它。
PROFESSOR: Let's not do the math.
教授：我们不做数学。
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
It's really, really good.
真的，真的很好。
So these are used for all sorts of practical problems, all
因此，这些用于各种实际问题，
the way from branch predictors in processors, to databases.
从处理器中的分支预测变量到数据库的方式。
AUDIENCE: So is it better than 1%?
听众：那么它是否比1％好？
Do you know that, at least?
至少你知道吗？
PROFESSOR: Oh yeah, for practical uses, this gets you,
教授：是的，对于实际用途，这可以使您，
I think to 1% of 1% of 1%.
我认为是1％的1％。
So usually, put a Bloom filter before a really expensive
因此，通常情况下，将Bloom过滤器放在价格昂贵的
check, and the Bloom filter gets rid of most
检查，Bloom过滤器将摆脱大多数
of the false positives.
误报。
And then you have a few more where
然后你还有一些地方
you do the more expensive check.
您进行更昂贵的检查。
Okay, does this make sense?
好吧，这有意义吗？
Any questions?
任何问题？
AUDIENCE: Do you more optimal if you repeated this Bloom
观众：如果您重复此Bloom，您会更理想吗？
filter independently of the other one,
独立于另一个过滤器
with more hash functions in that memory structure?
在该内存结构中具有更多哈希函数？
PROFESSOR: I think doubling the memory size is better.
教授：我认为将内存大小加倍会更好。
So two filters is the same as having two n bits.
因此，两个滤波器等同于具有两个n位。
I think doubling gives you better results, always.
我认为加倍总是可以为您带来更好的结果。
OK, so general stuff.
好，一般的东西。
We're going to have a lot of conceptual questions,
我们将有很多概念性问题，
so please make sure, again, make sure that for everything
所以请再次确保所有内容
that we did, go through the problem.
我们所做的，解决问题。
Understand the problem, know that there is a solution.
了解问题，知道有解决方案。
Know the running time, maybe know
知道运行时间，也许知道
how to implement the solution.
如何实施解决方案。
Don't worry so much about the proof.
不必太担心证明。
We're going to have some problems where
我们将在哪里遇到一些问题
you have to come up with new things on your own,
你必须自己想出新的东西，
so get a good night's sleep before the exam.
因此，考试前要睡个好觉。
Really, if you have five hours left,
真的，如果您还有五个小时，
then you have to choose between sleeping five hours
那你必须选择睡五个小时
or reading notes for five hours--
或阅读笔记五个小时
AUDIENCE: Drink caffeine.
听众：喝咖啡因。
PROFESSOR: It's not going to help,
教授：这无济于事，
so caffeine actually helps you stay up,
因此咖啡因实际上可以帮助您熬夜，
but it decreases your performance.
但是会降低您的效果。
And so if you're on caffeine, you're not going to think.
因此，如果您使用咖啡因，就不会思考。
You can regurgitate stuff, but you can't think.
您可以反省东西，但您无法考虑。
So caffeinating yourself is a--
因此，咖啡因是-
AUDIENCE: I thought it was like it gives you concentration.
听众：我以为这让你专心。
PROFESSOR: So there's an optimum amount of sleep and caffeine
教授：所以有充足的睡眠和咖啡因
combination.
组合。
If you don't sleep and caffeinate yourself,
如果你不睡觉就喝咖啡
I guarantee that you will not solve
我保证你不会解决
any of the problems that require new algorithms.
任何需要新算法的问题。
AUDIENCE: Caffeine just squirts adrenaline in your brain.
听众：咖啡因只会在您的大脑中喷出肾上腺素。
It doesn't do anything else.
它什么也没做。
PROFESSOR: So the thing is the memory is going to be better.
教授：所以问题是记忆会更好。
If all you're doing is memorization stuff,
如果你只是做背诵的东西，
then it's going to be better.
那就会更好。
So you're going to do well on the pattern matching stuff.
因此，您将在模式匹配方面做得很好。
But when your brain is panicking,
但是当你的大脑惊慌时，
you're not going to come up with new solutions, right?
您不会提出新的解决方案，对吗？
Usually, you have a problem, a hard problem.
通常，您有问题，很难解决。
You're thinking about it, and then at some point
您正在考虑，然后在某个时候
when you're relaxed, like when you're in the shower
当你放松的时候，比如在洗澡的时候
or when you wake up you're like, crap, I found a solution.
或当您醒来时，就像垃圾，我找到了解决方案。
So the brain finds solutions when it's relaxed,
因此，当大脑放松时，大脑会找到解决方案，
not when it's like, holy shit, holy shit, holy shit.
不是那样的时候，圣屎，圣屎，圣屎。
And adrenaline gets it in that mood.
肾上腺素使它充满那种心情。
That's what it does.
这就是它的作用。
And that's what caffeine does in the end.
这就是咖啡因最终的作用。
So a little bit of caffeine might help you get up
所以一点咖啡因可能会帮助你起床
and get you running, but don't caffeinate
让你跑步，但不要咖啡因
yourself to not sleep the entire night.
自己不要整夜睡觉。
That's probably going to make you bomb the hard questions.
这可能会让您炸开难题。
Good luck on Friday.
星期五好运。
Eat candy.
吃糖果。